# SIU MAN HO

Expected salary: \$15,000 - \$25,000 (negotiable)

Availability: After 1 June 2022

joesiu.github.io/portfolio

+852 69232500

## PROFILE

Passionate in 3D design and game development. Strong understanding of creating 3D assets for both offline rendering and for real-time game usage. Familiar with PBR workflows, and have experience in modeling, texturing, shading, lighting, rendering, and animation.

# EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science In Creative Media (Games Stream)
City University of Hong Kong (2018-2022)

### **EXPERIENCE**

**3D Game Designer (Summer Intern) | 10botics Limited** 2021/06 - 2021/08

- Create game ready 3D environments in Blender based on real life location
- Improve the gameplay for a Unity3D self-driving car simulator

## Freelance 3D Artist

2019 - 2022

• Worked with multiple clients, jobs including model conversion, architecture visualization, environment modeling and short animation creation

# SKILLS

#### Software

Illustrator -

11 11 25		
Unity3D		
Blender		
Photoshop		
Maya	_	
Substance		
Painter		
Premiere	•	

## **PROJECTS**

#### **Bopulation** (Final year project)

A 3D side-scrolling sci-fi game for PC, most 3D assets are modeled in Blender, textured in Substance Painter, and lighting and material added in Unity3D

#### Japan Alley

A 3D time-lapse animation based on an alley in Kyoto, with over 200+ sales on CGTrader. Made with Blender, Substance Painter, Photoshop, and Premiere

# **Final Class**

A 1-minute 3D photo-realistic animation made in Maya, Blender, Substance Painter, Photoshop, and Premiere

#### Merge Screen

A 3D split-screen game made in Blender and Unity3D, won the best "UI/UX" award at CityU SIG Playful Media Showcase